# KODY DUDLEY

# SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

## CONTACT

208-703-5423

https://github.com/kodydudley

<u>kodymdudley@gmail.com</u>

linkedin.com/in/kodymdudley/

### SUMMARY

A Software Developer with experience building full stack software applications. Over 500+ hours of hands-on training in multiple frameworks. 3+ years experience in management with one year focusing on project management prior to becoming a software developer.

#### SKILLS

- HTML
  C#/.Net
- CSS MongoDB
- BootStrap
   Mongoose
- JavaScript
   MySQL
- ...,..
- Vue.js Scrum
- Node.jsPartner Programming

#### **APPLICATIONS**

## moment

An application designed to help track and manage goals. It also allowed users to challenge other users to compete with each other.

# Roles

- Product Owner
- Scrum Master
- Developer

## Tech Stack

- Vue.js
- JavaScript
- MongoDB BootStrap

## Organyze

A unique version of a KanBan Board that allows users to create lists, tasks, and comments. *Roles* 

- Product Owner
- Developer

### Tech Stack

- Vue.jsJavaScript
- MongoDB
   BootStrap

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Software Development Student, CodeWorks Sept 2020- Present

- Collaborated with 3 other developers building a full stack application for tracking goals and challenging other
- Practiced Partner Programming to ensure efficiency and timely completion
- Debugged coding errors and communicated with peers and seniors regarding unknown errors
- Built several applications utilizing various technologies
- Implemented Scrum practices with team applications
- · Utilized Figma to create mock-ups of design features
- Integrated AuthO for user authentication on applications
- Worked with multiple APIs to integrate with applications
- Acted as a Product Owner and Scrum Master during capstone project building a full stack application

## Account Coordinator, SlideGenius

May 2019 - April 2020

- Ensure that all graphic design projects are delivered ontime, within scope, and within budget
- Develop a detailed project plan to monitor and track progress for all internal design projects
- Perform risk management to minimize project risks to ensure projects were completed on time and within budget
- Meet budgetary objectives and adjust project constraints based on financial analysis
- Assist in the definition of project scope and objectives, involving all relevant stakeholders and ensuring technical feasibility

## **Account Manager,** FirePoint Solutions Sept 2018 - May 2019

- Introduce clients to our Customer Relationship Management platform built for real estate agents
- Strategically use time management to handle phone calls, emails, and incoming chats.
- Handle between 50-70 emails, 10-20 live chats, and 20+ phone calls daily
- Deescalate upset customers that could potentially cancel their service.
- Troubleshoot any and all problems within the CRM.

## **EDUCATION**

Certificate of Completion, CodeWorks -Full Stack Software Development January 2021

Bachelor's Business Administration, Boise State University 2018